IVANA BAVIN-GOMEZ-SAN BASILIO

ABOUT

Focused and quick-learning Software Engineer with 3 years of experience in computer science, programming, and UX design for various projects. Detailed oriented and eager to learn new technologies. Problem solver with demonstrated success analyzing issues and creating quick solutions that lead to a positive effect. Motivated, hardworking, and reliable team player.

More than 15 years of experience in the music and video industry as a producer, composer, engineer, vocalist, and teacher.

PROFESSIONAL CAREER

SOFWTARE ENGINEER AT XYPRO, SIMI VALLEY, CA, APRIL 2017 - PRESENT

Role: Developer for XSW and MERLON products MARS and SQLXPress **Responsibilities:** Fixing bugs, creating enhancements and new features, helping with deployment.

Other responsibilities: Lead of POCs. Examples: moving to ipWorks. Moving repository from Team Coherence to Gitlab.

SHALEE PRODUCTIONS, AGOURA HILLS, CA, 2010 - PRESENT

Role: Owner/founder, accounting, project supervision, client relations **Responsibilities:**

Music composition and production, studio, and field audio engineer. Private instructor: music, voice, piano, production, music software.

Other responsibilities: Artist Management.

Clients: City of Agoura Hills, EMI records Spain, Lifetime Achievement Grammy Award recipient Paloma San Basilio, recording and independent artists, filmmakers, students.

TEACHER AND LECTURER, VARIOS LOCATIONS, 2005 - 2010

Music teacher at Edison Elementary School (Santa Monica, CA)

Private instructor (music, vocals, piano, production, Spanish) at various locations: Cornerstone Music Conservatory (CA), World Music (CA), Adagio Music School (MA), Gloria Dei Lutheran Church (RI) Lecturer at University of Southern California: "Effects of music practice and study on the brain's development, language acquisition and behavior".

VOCALIST AND PERFORMER, VARIOS LOCATIONS, 2000 - PRESENT

Lead and background singer for several musical ensembles, events and artists,

Studio singer for commercials and other professional sound recordings.

*More information about musical career available per request

SKILLS

COMPUTER SCIENCE:

Languages: Delphi, C#, VB.Net, SQL, Java, C++, Python, Bash, XAML,

HTML, CSS, Assembly (8051 Microprocessor).

3rd party components: C1 Component, Dev Express, ipWorks.

IDEs: Delphi, Eclipse, NetBeans, Visual Studio, Cygwin64

Databases: SQL Server, HP NonStop

Other: InstallShield, GitLab, SourceTree AWS, WordPress.

Agile lifecycle: Software: Jira, ALM, Confluence. Practice agile

development methodologies.

Technologies: git, GitLab, Bitbucket, GitHub, Sourcetree.

MUSIC AND VIDEO:

Skills: Music composition, arrangement, orchestration, music production, music engineering, proficient vocalist, keyboardist, taggeber, sanguritar, sound angineer, video editor.

teacher, songwriter, sound engineer, video editor.

Software: Photoshop, Final Cut, Adobe Premier, ProTools, Digital Performer, Cubase, Finale, Reason, Kontakt, Reactor, Absynth, Stylus

RMX, Garriton Personal Orchestra, Battery, Melodyne, etc.

BILINGUAL

English and Spanish.

ADMINISTRATION AND MANAGEMENT

Skills: Teamwork, Conflict Resolution, Critical Thinking, Decision Making, Problem Solving, Adaptability, Multitasking, Creative, Insightful, and Innovative.

Software: Visio, Microsoft Word, Excel, Power Point, Pages, Adobe

Acrobat.

EDUCATION

M.S. COMPUTER SCIENCE, CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY CHANNEL ISLANDS, CAMARILLO, ONGOING Current GPA 4.0

B.S. COMPUTER SCIENCE, CAIFORNIA LUTHERAN UNIVERSITY, THOUSAND OAKS, CA, 2018

Internal GPA 3.9.

Graduated Cum Laude and was awarded with the departmental distinction Received the outstanding student award in multiple classes

BUSINESS ENTREPRENEUR CERTIFICATE, WEV, SANTA BARBARA, CA, 2013

Certification by Women's Economic Ventures

B.A. FILMSCORING, BERKLEE COLLEGE OF MUSIC, BOSTON, MA, 2005

Graduated Cum Laude

B.A. CONTEMPORRAY WRITING & PRODUCTION, BERKLEE COLLEGE OF MUSIC, BOSTON, MA, 2005

Graduated Cum Laude